Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/vu-nguyen-065269177 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Business Development UX/UI Design Web Design

Certifications

Foundation of User Experience (UX) Design

Start the UX Design Process: Empathize, Define, and Ideate Introduction to Generative Al

Vu Nguyen

Staff UX/UI Design at Spartan Dev

Da Nang City, Vietnam

Summary

I have been working as a UI UX Designer and Product Designer for almost two years. I specialize in Website Responsive, Mobile User Interface and User Experience (UI/UX), Strongly e-commerce, cms, product designs for both iOS and Android platforms. So far I've worked with individual clients as well as fresh entrepreneurs and reputed companies. I'm here to provide my service to make your product amazing.

Experience

Spartan Dev Staff UI/UX Designer September 2022 - Present (2 years 7 months) Los Angeles, California, United States

Ecomdy
UX Designer
July 2021 - October 2023 (2 years 4 months)
Da Nang City, Vietnam

SK Sumikura UI Designer November 2021 - December 2021 (2 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

MOR Software JSC UX/UI Designer June 2020 - July 2021 (1 year 2 months) Da Nang City, Vietnam

SmartDev

3 years 1 month

UX/UI Designer
January 2019 - March 2020 (1 year 3 months)

Page 1 of 2

Da Nang City, Vietnam

Manual Testing

August 2018 - December 2018 (5 months)

Da Nang City, Vietnam

Software developer

March 2017 - August 2018 (1 year 6 months)

Da Nang City, Vietnam

Education

Duy Tan University

Bachelor of Information Technology, Computer Software

Engineering · (2013 - 2017)

Graphic design training center

illustrator course certificate, illustrator design · (2019 - 2020)